[{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980836577,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":9634,"timeElapsed":82149},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980842806,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":6226,"timeElapsed":88378},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980846656,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":3846,"timeElapsed":92228},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980851480,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":4821,"timeElapsed":97052},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980854432,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":2948,"timeElapsed":100004},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980856734,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":2300,"timeElapsed":102306},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980859564,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":2827,"timeElapsed":105136},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980947050,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":87481,"timeElapsed":192622},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980949526,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":2472,"timeElapsed":195098},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980955821,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":5414,"timeElapsed":201393},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980994274,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":38449,"timeElapsed":239846},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980998570,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":4293,"timeElapsed":244142},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981002828,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":4256,"timeElapsed":248400},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981005766,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2935,"timeElapsed":251337},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981034986,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":29218,"timeElapsed":280558},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981038224,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":3235,"timeElapsed":283796},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981044678,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":6451,"timeElapsed":290250},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981047197,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2517,"timeElapsed":292769},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981051842,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":3915,"timeElapsed":297414},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981054376,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":2532,"timeElapsed":299948},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981058392,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4013,"timeElapsed":303964},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981062678,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4283,"timeElapsed":308250},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981068138,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":5458,"timeElapsed":313710},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981070711,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":2570,"timeElapsed":316283},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981074288,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3575,"timeElapsed":319860},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981076779,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":2486,"timeElapsed":322350},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981079414,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2633,"timeElapsed":324986},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981082235,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2819,"timeElapsed":327807},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981090847,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":7967,"timeElapsed":336419},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981092975,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":2125,"timeElapsed":338547},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981096367,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3389,"timeElapsed":341939},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981099488,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3119,"timeElapsed":345060},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981103171,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3682,"timeElapsed":348743},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981106922,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":3747,"timeElapsed":352494},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981109392,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2468,"timeElapsed":354964},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981114541,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":5145,"timeElapsed":360113},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981118415,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":3872,"timeElapsed":363987},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981133534,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":14295,"timeElapsed":379106},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981139173,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":5636,"timeElapsed":384745},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981142819,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":3644,"timeElapsed":388391},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981147293,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":4473,"timeElapsed":392865},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981151367,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4073,"timeElapsed":396939},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981153086,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":1717,"timeElapsed":398658},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981158268,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":5179,"timeElapsed":403840},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981165865,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":7595,"timeElapsed":411437},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981167951,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":2085,"timeElapsed":413523},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981174569,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":5646,"timeElapsed":420141},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981177108,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":2537,"timeElapsed":422680},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981180611,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3501,"timeElapsed":426183},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981183008,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2393,"timeElapsed":428580},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981185992,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2981,"timeElapsed":431564},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981190198,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":4205,"timeElapsed":435770},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981192605,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":2405,"timeElapsed":438177},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981199251,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":6642,"timeElapsed":444823},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981202361,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":3106,"timeElapsed":447933},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981208681,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":5701,"timeElapsed":454253},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981210421,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":1737,"timeElapsed":455993},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981212707,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2283,"timeElapsed":458279},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981214708,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":1997,"timeElapsed":460280},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981217627,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2918,"timeElapsed":463199},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981220176,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":2545,"timeElapsed":465748},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981221707,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1528,"timeElapsed":467279},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981224599,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":2890,"timeElapsed":470171},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981229207,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":4606,"timeElapsed":474779},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981234441,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":4529,"timeElapsed":480012},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981236826,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":2383,"timeElapsed":482398},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981239054,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":2226,"timeElapsed":484626},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981241638,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":2583,"timeElapsed":487210},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981246296,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4655,"timeElapsed":491868},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981250460,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":4161,"timeElapsed":496031},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981254058,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":3596,"timeElapsed":499630},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981268964,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":14902,"timeElapsed":514536},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981271142,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":2176,"timeElapsed":516714},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981278838,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":6802,"timeElapsed":524410},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981281327,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":2486,"timeElapsed":526899},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981283578,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":2249,"timeElapsed":529150},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981285005,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":1424,"timeElapsed":530576},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981286973,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1965,"timeElapsed":532545},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981290323,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":3348,"timeElapsed":535895},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981293809,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":3483,"timeElapsed":539381},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981296121,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2309,"timeElapsed":541692},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981299198,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":3077,"timeElapsed":544770},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981301638,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":2437,"timeElapsed":547209},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981308731,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":6397,"timeElapsed":554303},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981311402,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2668,"timeElapsed":556974},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981314321,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2916,"timeElapsed":559893},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981317103,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2780,"timeElapsed":562675},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981321478,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":4372,"timeElapsed":567050},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981324356,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":2875,"timeElapsed":569927},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981325965,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1607,"timeElapsed":571537},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981328620,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":2654,"timeElapsed":574192},{"subjectID":"f5cebaun9m","prolificID":"5a08c9a7f2e3460001edb063","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25fdaa828312e3e7d08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981331740,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3117,"timeElapsed":577312}]